lie like said welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep brother
James and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage Thou shalt
have no other gods before me thou
shallal not make unto thee any Graven
image or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above or that is in the
earth beneath or that is in the water
under the Earth Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for I the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquity of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that taketh his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shalt thou labor and do
all thy work but the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God in it Thou
shalt not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy man's servant nor
thy maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates for in
six days the Lord made Heaven and Earth
the sea and all that in them is and
resteth the seventh day wherefore the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day and
hollowed it honor thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee Thou shalt not kill Thou shalt not
commit adultery Thou shalt not steal
thou shall not bear false witness
against thy neighbor Thou shalt not
covet thy neighbor's house thou shallal
not covet thy neighbor's wife nor his
man's servant nor his maid servant nor
his Ox nor his ass nor anything that is
thy
neighbors that scripture reading came
from Exodus the 20th chapter verses 1
through 17 may the Lord add a blessing
to the
reading of his word and Q&A this
evening all right amen amen so here on
question and answer you can ask us a
question and we'll answer it according
to the King James Bible and if we cannot
find the answer we will seek further
counsel to bring you an answer at a
later time keep in mind that all vague
questions will not be answered and all
long scripture questions will not be
answered for time sake but we may be
able to point you in the direction of a
DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling office so please for time say be
as direct as possible with your
questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible no other Bibles will be
acknowledged on this program also keep
in mind that this is a live stream and
you may begin to send in your questions
at this time even questions that pertain
to everlasting life we ask that you keep
them to a two scripture maximum but let
me introduce you to family that's on the
panel this evening we got brother Dre
good evening brother Jerome gra in peace
Brother Julius good evening everybody
brother James good evening everyone
sister
Deborah good
evening
Sean good evening and we have the guest
caller with us and I'm brother Cornell
sister Deborah let us begin with our
first question of the evening
uh yes there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A 103 MJ
asks in Ezekiel 28 it says that Satan is
a cherub but in Isaiah 6 verse2 says
it's a
seraphim why all right cheram in one
book sarim in another why that brother
Jerome well yes um Satan he is a cherub
Angel but uh cherub angels have more
than just one title um not only are they
called cherubim Angels they're called
seraphim as well they're also called
teraphim but they still the same type of
Angel okay let's go read the verse that
you gave in the
Isaiah 6 verse
2 above it stood the seraphim each one
had six wings with Twain he covered his
face and with Twain he covered his feet
and with Twain he did
fly okay now that covers one type of
Angel and that's a cherub Angel but once
again they have more than one title so
not they call sarap they also call uh
terap same type of Angel excuse me and
they all got six wings even though it
might sound like Ezekiel said they got
four they actually got six wings they
have two wings that they got stretched
upward those are the two they fly with
and they got two on one side to cover
their bodies and they got two on the
other side to cover their bodies okay
six wings in
total that's all I got
on all right well I want I want to throw
something in every time every time the
Lord showed up these angels these Cher
angels with now to let you know what he
put around him uh uh is the same one
don't we go into uh uh Genesis the third
chapter and start reading at verse
22 Genesis 3 and 22
and the Lord God said behold the man has
become as one of us to know good and
evil and now least he put forth his hand
and take also of the tree of life and
eat and live
forever
therefore the God sent him forth from
the Garden of Eden to till the ground
from when he was taken so he drove out
the man
and placed him at the east of the Garden
of Eden cherubims and a flaming sword
which turned every way to keep the way
of way of the tree of
life I see Jesus the tree of life so no
matter what they call what you call them
when they show up is still the same
thing the Cher Angel like in Revelation
the fourth chapters call them just four
four Beast other place is four living
creatures but in order to know that
these are the same you have to go back
to Genesis and find out what the Lord
put around
him protect your way of the truee of
life because he is the true of life so
like like uh uh uh Jerome said no matter
what name they are is they called is
still these same chair of
angels yep all right we hope that
answered your question is we continue to
move on to our next one yes also 103 MJ
asks why does iog say the
weu will have 31
armies Julius why do they say that they
have 31
armies U according to the scripture it's
going to be 10 Power
Nations 10 Power Nations but there are
28 member nations uh there are 28
member nation in the Western European
Union which is the Wu with Croatia being
the latest one to join uh in 2013 and
joined the euro in 2023 so therefore
it's it it's 28 member nations now but
in the end according to scripture it
will be 10 uh Power Nations let's go to
Daniel the thir chapter and you you have
to read the whole story or you can get
the lesson that the Israel of God has
Daniel you said Daniel 3 sir yeah Daniel
Daniel 2 I'm sorry Daniel
2 okay Daniel 2 because Nebuchadnezzar
had a dream and Daniel interpreted a
dream it was about the whole uh
composite Gentile Dynasty starting with
the head of gold to the uh the feet with
the T toes in it part strong and part
clay let's go to Daniel right to the
point Daniel 2 and 42 go ahead
brother and as the toes of the feet were
part of iron and part of clay so the
kingdom shall be partly strong and
partly broken and where strong Nations
and weak Nations go ahead and whereas
thou sawest iron mixed with myy Clay
they shall mingle themselves with the
seed of men but they shall not cleave
one to another even as iron is not mixed
with Clay give me one more verse because
we're talking about end time prophecy
now go ahead and in the days of these
Kings shall the god of Heaven set up a
kingdom which shall never be destroyed
and the enough brother you could read
the rest of it on your own but in the
days of these Kings we come down from
the head Babylon all the way down to the
T to which is the Western European Union
Power Nations quickly Revelation 17 now
these 10 toes that's going in our day
and time is the 10
horns okay and Revelation 17 and verse
12 and the T horns which thou saw us are
10 Kings which have received no Kingdom
of yet but receive power as kings one
hour with the Beast and that's going to
be the great tribul that that one hour
uh prophetically can represent the Great
Tribulation period which is 3 and a half
years but it's going to be 10 Power
Nations of Western Europe so therefore
they got 28 members uh they got 28
members now and they got seven more
waiting to join and also Ukraine is
trying to join and uh uh some more are
trying to join but these are Western
Europe Nations so the we don't say at
the i31 we say it's going to be 10 Power
Nations according to the scriptures we
know they got a whole bunch of them in
there now but in the end it will only be
10 that would give their power to the
beast that's all I got on that brother
Corel okay IAD yes
sir now these 10 nations are going to
rule over all the Western Europe and the
reason the 31 armor was mentioned is
because it was written in the newspaper
sometime clipping some years back but if
you want to know for sure you can go on
the internet and find out these guys
right now they have 31 armies at their
beckon call but these te over all the
Western Europe and you can find that
written also on the
internet so
that's all right thank you guest Co all
right we hope that answered your
question as we continue to move on to
our next moving on y then Israel ask for
you to explain second Peter 1 ver 17 and
18 second Peter 1 vers 17 and 18 brother
James let's go
there because this is talking about
Jesus and this is talking about the
father also whose name is
Jesus let's go and read pick it up at
that verse 17
for he received from God the Father
honor and Glory when there came such a
voice to him from the excellent Glory
this is my beloved Son in whom I am well
pleased so this is Jesus the one that
came to die for the sins of the world he
received from God the Father honor and
glory and a voice Came From Heaven
saying this is my beloved Son in whom I
am well pleased read 18 and this voice
which came from heaven we heard when we
were with him in the Holy Mount so let's
go back to um Matthew the thir chapter
let's see when this actually happened
here let's go back to Matthew the thir
chapter because this was at the baptism
of Jesus when this voice Came From
Heaven which was an angel can't say it
was the father's voice because we never
heard his voice at any time nor seen his
shape
because the brothers that was there say
we heard his voice so we know that had
to been an angel so all right Matthew
three and let's pick it up at verse 13
because this is when John was baptizing
and Jesus came to him to be baptized
also and let's see what John said verse
13 go ahead brother then cometh Jesus
From Galilee the Jordan unto John to be
baptized of him but but John forbade him
saying I have need to be baptized of
thee and comest thou to me I see what
John was saying go ahead and Jesus
answering said unto him suffer it to be
so now for thus it becometh us to
fulfill all righteousness then he
suffered him yes and Jesus when he was
baptized went up straightway out of the
water and lo the heavens were open unto
him and he saw the spirit of God
descending like a dove and lightning
upon him and
what and lo a voice from Heaven saying
this is my beloved Son in whom I am well
pleased yeah so this was at Jesus
baptism when he got baptized and then
this voice said this is my beloved Son
in whom I am well pleased was that the
bap ISM of
Jesus and that's all I
got and we hope that that answer oh I'm
sorry guest caller go right
ahead it was said in another place too
where uh Jesus said that there are some
that uh uh should not die be death until
they see the son of man coming in his
kingdom and said I think it said eight
days later they took John and Peter and
some people up in the mountain
and
transfigured Matthew
17 okay we go read it Matthew
17 yeah you pick it up at
one good well actually you can start in
the 16th verse and and and read verse
27- 28 and then go into the 17th chapter
the 16 16th chapter read verse 2728 and
then go right into the 17th chapter
for the son of man shall come in the
glory of his father with his angels and
then he shall reward every man according
to his Works verily I say unto you there
be some standing here which shall not
taste of death till they see the son of
man coming in his
kingdom and and after six days Jesus
taketh Peter James and John his brother
and bringeth them up and an high
mountain apart and was transfigured
before them and his face did shine as
the sun and his reignment was white as
the
light and behold there appeared unto
them Moses and Elias talking with him
then answered Peter and said unto Jesus
Lord it is good for us to be here if
thou Wilt let us make he the Tabernacles
one for thee and one for Moses and one
for
Elias while he yet spake Behold a bright
Cloud overshadowed them and behold a
voice of the cloud which said this is my
beloved Son in whom I am well pleased
hear ye him yes and when the disci yeah
so that that is when all of the uh uh
that's when all of the uh uh 12 all when
the disciples were with him okay right
right so yeah it was other than that the
baptism it was at the Transfiguration
too right uhuh see at the baptism uh
Jesus hadn't picked his
Apostles right but here is after he had
picked his Apostles so he said it twice
yes all right good add on and we hope
that answered your question as we move
on to our next moving on Zion says can
you explain Amos three verses one and
two are the children of Israel the only
ones that are punished for their sins
what about the other nations they sin
also all right brother Drake share some
light on that Amos 31 and2 about the
punishment of Israel let's go read that
brother James
Amos 3: 1 and two read it when you get
there
brother he the word that the Lord has
spoken against you oh children of Israel
against the whole family which I brought
up from the land of Egypt saying you
only have I known of all the families of
the earth therefore I will punish you
for all your iniquities yep so verses
here these verses one and two
is directed to the children of Israel
the words that the Lord spoken against
them so he is speaking about the
children of Israel and he say you only
have I known of all the families of the
earth therefore will I punish you for
all your iniquity as it pertains to
other nations let's go into Isaiah 13
Isaiah 13 and we going to read verses 9-
Isaiah 13
9-1 when you get it brother James go
ahead behold the day of the Lord cometh
cruel both with wrath and fierce anger
to lay the land desolate and he shall
destroy the Sinners thereof out of it
now notice he didn't say Israel he said
Sinners go ahead for the stars of Heaven
and the constellations thereof shall not
give their light the sun shall not be
dark the sun shall be darkened and his
going forth and the moon shall not cause
her light to
shine and I will punish the world for
their evil and the wicked for their
iniquity and I will cause the arrogancy
of The Proud to cease and will lay low
the Hess of the Terrible
he says I will punish the world for
their iniquity the world so let's go to
one other place let's go to Second
Thessalonians the first chapter 2
Thessalonians the first
chapter and uh pick it up at
verse
six uh seven seven verse seven okay yes
sir go ahead and to you who are troubled
rest with us when the Lord Jesus shall
be re revealed from heaven with his
mighty
angels and and flaming fire taking
Vengeance on them that know not God and
that obey not the gospel of our Lord
Jesus
Christ who shall be punished with
Everlasting destruction from the
presence of the Lord and from the glory
of his power
so the Lord is going to come and he is
going to judge the world Israel is
getting dealt with for their iniquity
and if they we don't tighten it up we
gonna get dealt with in this time as
well so I hope that that that answers
your
question brother Cornell that's
it all right thank you brother hope that
answered their question and let us keep
it moving sister deil
yes keeping it moving Malik Shakur says
I know it was said that it's okay to
have
tattoos as long as they are not for the
dead what about tattooing a cross onto
your
skin so guess Cara can you tattoo a
cross on your
skin you're not supposed to cross is a
Roman death tool have nothing to do with
Jesus it don't represent Jesus Jesus uh
people were being uh crucified by the
Romans before Jesus and people was
crucified by the Romans after Jesus you
have a historical fact is when Titus
took Jerusalem down he was crucified up
to 500 people a day have nothing to do
with Jesus but if it did have something
to do with Jesus still you shouldn't
have it and this is why let's go Exodus
the 20th chapter read verses 3 and
4 Exodus
20 verses 3 and
4 Exodus 20 veres 3 and 4 Thou shalt
have no other gods before me thou shall
not make unto thee any Graven image or
any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above or that is in the earth
beneath or that is in the water under
the Earth
now e now across you know even when God
spoke to Israel he spoke to Israel out
of the smoke because he didn't want them
to see him because he didn't want them
to make no image of him let alone an
image that's supposed to represent him
so no you're not supposed to have a uh
cross tattoo on you that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question next
question next question Brother Jay says
in Isaiah 46
verse1 can you explain this scripture
who it is what is his purpose and where
is he coming from and where is he
going all right who is he what is his
purpose and where is he coming from and
they say Isaiah
4611 guest carer can you share some
light don't read it
46 Isaiah 46
and11 calling a ravenous bird from the
East the man that executeth my counsel
from a far country yay I have spoken it
I will also bring it to pass I have
purposed it I will also do
it now this this this bird is just a
metaphor when he said a man that's
talking about the one that's going to be
leading Eastern Europe Russia is going
to be the one let's go into Isaiah the
13th chapter we're going to read verses
1 through
6 Isaiah 13 veres
1-6 the burden of Babylon which Isaiah
the son of Amos did see lift ye up a
banner upon the high mountain exalt The
Voice unto to them shake the hand that
they may go into the gates of the Nobles
I have commanded my Sanctified ones I
have also called my mighty ones for mine
anger even them that rejoice in my
highness that the noise of a multitude
in the mountains like as a great people
a tumultuous noise of the kingdoms of
Nations gathered together the Lord of
hosts must the host of the battle
they come from a far country from the
end of Heaven even the Lord and the
weapons of his indignation to destroy
the whole land how ye for the day of the
Lord is at hand it shall come as a
destruction from the
almighty so now that's what's going to
lead up to the war of Armageddon because
Western Europe is going to attack
Eastern Europe Russia re really cuz you
can see it getting ready to happen now
but some thing have to happen before it
go down but the whole thing this Army
that the Lord talking about this Russian
army is the Lord's army he have
Sanctified them to do this
sanctification mean he set them apart to
do this great job and he's going to do
this on the day of the Lord when he get
ready to come now let's go to Joel the
thir chapter second chapter look at this
same Army two and we going to read one
through three then we going to skip
Joel
2 okay Joel chapter 2 starting at what
scripture
again read the three
okay blow ye the trumpet in Zion and
sound an alarm in my Holy Mountain let
the inhabitants of the land tremble for
the day of the Lord cometh for it is
nigh at hand a day of this is the this
is the same day of the Lord that we just
got through reading about okay this is
when the Lord come but he going in this
day he going to bring an army this
Eastern Army which is Russia and her
allies everybody on that's east of the
ukra river going to bring them and deal
with and they going to be
uh attacking Western Europe which attack
them first go ahead a day of darkness
and of gloominess a day of clouds and of
thick Darkness as the morning spread
upon the mountains a great people and a
strong there have not been ever the like
neither shall be anym after it even to
the years of many
generations a
fire you know you
notice we read Isaiah 13 first he say
come from the end of Heaven which is the
end of Earth Earth at the first Heaven
do that mean you go further east when
you get out of Russia you're in the west
so now there a great people strong and
look what look how destructive they
going to be go ahead a fire devoureth
before them and behind them a flame
burneth the land is as the Garden of
Eden before them and behind them a
desolate Wilderness yay and nothing
shall Escape
them that's when they come across that
you this River with China and everybody
EAS of there skip down to verse 11 and
read it and the Lord shall utter his
voice before his army for his Camp is
very great for he is strong that
executeth his word for the day of the
Lord is great and very terrible and who
can abide
it okay so now this great Army the Lord
is going to bring that's going to end up
being the wall of Armageddon that's when
the Lord is going to intervene through
now through the the nation that they
just talking about the head of the
nation of Russia coming from where come
from Eastern Europe on the way where to
Western Europe to attack Babylon the
great which is nowadays called the
European Union and her
allies okay that's
it all right will be a terrible time
indeed all right right hope that
answered your question as we move on to
our
next next question be alert says why do
we pray with our hands stretched out
versus closed Palms together does it
matter brother Jerome I've seen him do
both what you say
brother um we we we HED the bet because
we read in the Old Testament and the new
test minut if you praying with your
hands stressed up you know uh Lord here
Solomon um did it and you can read in uh
Timothy not that the Lord won't hear
your prayer if you don't pray that way
CU he'll hear your prayer if you prayer
silently don't utter a word just think
the prayer here hear okay so it's just a
another way you can prayer with somewhat
H the but bet and we do it because we've
read it that's why we do it you know uh
let's go to 1 Timothy Chapter 2 and read
verse
8 1 Timothy chapter 2 verse
8 Timothy 2 verse 8
okay I will therefore that men pray
everywhere lifting up holy hands without
wrath and doubting yeah so when I read
this that's the reason why I start
praying that way I'm trying to hge the
bet that's all you know but Hannah uh
she in the Old Testament she prayed
within her mind she just she was moving
her lips but you could hear the what she
was saying and Lord heard her prayer you
know so that's all I got on there
anybody want to add something they can't
yeah they had the option to pray either
way like you say brother the Lord will
hear them yes sir all right
sister Deborah we moveing to our next
question yes Miss Wade asked in Amos 9
verse 7 what did the Lord mean when he
said are ye not as the children of
Ethiopians unto me oh children of
Israel brother Julius are you not as the
children of the Ethiopians unto me what
did that mean
come off mute
brother thank you let's go to that
scripture brother James Amos 9 and7 the
Lord compared his people uh to the
Ethiopians in terms of color but the
scripture talk about by the way how he
delivered Israel also when you get it
Amos 9 and S then we go one more place
go ahead and read it
not as children of the Ethiopians unto
me oh children of Israel sayeth the Lord
have not I brought up Israel out of the
land of Egypt and the Philistines from
captor and the syrians from
kir so the Lord is showing us his power
and he's showing us how he delivered
Israel and how he put other nations in
their places and he's identifying his
people by color
let's go to Jeremiah the 13th
chapter the word AE when the Greek
conquered uh the holy land they saw
these people uh they said these people
are aops which means burnt
skinned dark
faces Jeremiah 13 Jeremiah 13 and read
verse 23 Jeremiah 13 and 23 this how we
know that it was comparing this people
to color go ahead can the Ethiopian
change his skin can the Ethiopian change
his skin he burnt skin dark face no he
can't change his skin go ahead or the
leopard his spots uhuh then then may ye
also do good that are accustomed to do
evil so he's showing the color of true
Israel true Israel is black folks so
therefore uh is a black people so
therefore
this is why he didn't compare his people
to uh Moses pass for an
Egyptian and Paul so did Paul pass for
an
Egyptian but he compared his people to a
people that could that because he knew
that uh uh the Arabs would come up and
take over the land of Egypt and call
themselves Egyptians the word Egypt
means black land
but he compared the people to the
Ethiopians darkk burnt face are people
that can never change their skin and
nobody else can take that color so you
could you could take identity theft but
you cannot change the color so therefore
that scripture is
about comparing the People Israel in
color to Ethiopians that's all I got
brother
Corel all right thank you for that
brother hope that answered their
question sister Deborah time check as we
move on yes the time is
806 Rand 64 said yes can you please
explain the scripture Colossians 2
verse6 about keeping the Sabbath while
some people say this scripture is
talking about you don't have to keep the
Sabbath don't listen to them brother
James go to the
Colossians okay I'm there verse two and
verse 16 and then the guest caller is
going to weigh in from there what
chapter in Colossians chapter two
in verse
16 let no man therefore judge you in
meat or in drink or in respect of an
holy day or of the new moon or of the
Sabbath
days keep reading which are a shadow of
things to come but the body is of
Christ read let no man begal you of your
reward and a voluntary humility and
worshiping of angels intruding into
those things which he ha not seen verely
puffed up by his fleshly
mind now you got to remember that Paul
was writing to the to uh uh uh
Colossians these are not Israelites
gentil didn't keep no Sabbath days and
no kind even to this day they don't keep
Sabbath Day to Die uh uh
uh like Israel kep it so he was talking
to the Colossians but if Paul was trying
to tell you that uh uh not to keep the
Sabbath days and the high days then Paul
is a
hypocrite I'm show you why
I let's go into acts the 18th chapter
read verses 18-
23 acts
18 and 18- 23
and Paul after this there yet a good
while and then took his leave of the
Brethren and sailed then into Syria and
with him Priscilla and Aquilla having
shown his head in ceria where he had a
vow and he came to Ephesus and left them
there but he himself entered into the
synagogues and re and reasoned with the
Jews when they desired him to very long
time with them he consented not but B
them farewell saying I must by all means
keep this Feast that cometh in Jerusalem
but I will return again unto you if God
will and he sell from
Ephesus now look people want him to stay
there he said well look I got to go cuz
I'm going to try everything I can to be
in to keep this Feast that come up in
Jerusalem that's one of God's High days
and also is a Sabbath day now let go to
Acts 20 and read verse
16 Acts 20 and verse
16 for Paul had determined to Sail by
Ephesus because he would not spend the
time in Asia for he hastened if it were
possible for him to be in Jerusalem the
day of
Pentecost so why would he tell people
not to honor those days if he did
everything they can he can one time he
would stay in in uh in in Ephesus the
next time he wouldn't go through Ephesus
both time one to keep the feast other
Lord you know the prop was unleavened
bread and then in Pentecost which also
the Feast of Pentecost which also is a
Sabbath day but we go one other
place let's back up to acts 18 and read
verses one and Skip down to verse four
and read it
after these things Paul departed from
Athens and came to Corinth and he
reasoned in the synagogue every Sabbath
and persuaded the Jews and the Greeks
yes
sir I come in and say reason uh at the
synagogue with the Jews and then on
another day with the Greeks uh-uh he did
it on the Sabbath day why because Paul
kept the Sabbath day Paul kept on all of
the high
days so Paul is not telling people that
they should not keep these this is the
uh Gentile interpretation which he have
passed on to uh uh this modern day
preacher all I have to say all
right hope that answered your question
as we move on to our
next next question jjun North for says
can you please explain the parable in
Luke 17:
6-10 Dre can you explain that Parable in
Luke 17
6-10 yeah let's go read uh that Luke
17 and uh pick it up at
verse
five read verses five and six James go
ahead and the apostles said unto the
Lord increase our faith and the Lord
lord said if ye had Faith as a grain of
mustard seed ye might say unto the S
sycamine tree be thou plucked up by the
root and be thou planted in the sea and
it should obey you so now Jesus is
telling them after they asked him to
increase their faith he said if you had
the faith of a mustard seed this is what
you will be able to do and what what you
will call for within his will it shall
be done
now verse seven on is dealing with a
little something else so let's go ahead
read verse 7 to10 go ahead but which of
you having a servant plowing or feeding
cattle will say unto him by and by when
he has come from the field go and sit
down to meet and will not rather say
unto him make ready wherewith I may Su
and gir thyself and serve me till I have
eaten and drunken and afterward Thou
shalt eat and drink doeth he that the
that do I'm sorry doeth he think that
the servant because he did the things
that were commanded him I troll not so
now he's saying here he
said but which of you having a vant
plowing feeding cattle will say unto him
by and by when he has come from the
field go sit down to eat to to me and
will not rather say to him make ready
wherewith I may up and GTH thyself and
serve me till I have eaten and drunken
and after word thou shalt eat and drink
and he said do he does he thank that
servant because he did the things that
were commanded of him he said I think
not that's what Tron not mean I don't
think that he would because that is the
servant's duty and a faith servant will
do their Duty verse 10 brother go ahead
so likewise ye when ye shall have done
all these things which are commanded you
say we are unprofitable servants we have
done that which was our duty to do so
hey it is our duty to serve God as
servants and that is what it is is our
duty to do in terms of where God brought
us from we were unprofitable servants
but when you serve God Faithfully you no
longer an unprofitable servant but you
are not a servant to Bo of
yourself your boast is in him not of
yourself I hope that
helps all right thank you for that
brother hope that answered that question
as we move on to our
next next question jalah says my
grandson which is autistic is 12 and has
only heard about God from me would like
to bring him to the lesson is there a
class for
pre-teens all right so we glad that you
have been teaching your grandson about
God and yes we do have a class that's
for the pre-teens and only thing that we
require and ask is that each child not
disrupt the class or other children
while the class is going on but yes we
do have a class for pre-teen
all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
moving on we can talk right here says
did Jesus go to hell and what for if he
did yes carer can you weigh in on that
question about
Jesus no it didn't go to
hell
hell uh in certain case has come from
the word shuel which mean the
grave so he went to the
grave now let's go and show you what I'm
talking about let's go into Psalms
chapter
16 and we're going to read from verse 8
through 10 16
8-10
okay I have set the lord always before
me because he is at my right hand I
shall not be moved therefore my heart is
glad and my glory rejoiceth My Flesh
also shall Rest In Hope for thou will
not leave my soul in Hell neither wil
thou suffer thine Holy One to see
corruption see now that's when he when
he held here talking about the grave
that's why he said uh uh you will not uh
uh you will not leave my soul in Hell
which is the gra
suffer your Holy One to seek corruption
in other words you're not going to let
my body
decompose so that is talking about the
grave now let's go into Psalms the 30th
chapter and read 1
through3 Psalms
31-3 I will extol thee O Lord for thou
Has Lifted Me Up and has not made my
foes to Rejoice over me oh Lord my God I
Cried unto thee and thou has healed me
oh Lord thou has brought up my soul from
the grave thou has kept me alive that I
should not go down to the
pit go right there one he said you will
not leave my soul in hell and here he
said you have brought up my soul from
the grave in other words the word l in
this particular place is simply talking
about the grave Jesus died and he went
into the grave and then the Lord raised
him up out of the Grave that's all I
have to say all right hope that answered
your question there as we move on to our
next
question moving on David stanel as the
lady Jesus met at the well was she an
Israelite lady that Jesus met at the
well was she an Israelite brother Julius
no she was not an Israelite
she was not an Israelite she was
somebody that had been whose ancestors
had been placed there let's go to John
the 4th chapter St John
4 St John 4 and we gonna pick this up at
verse five brother James St John 4 and
five most likely she was a hamite but we
gonna see what the book say St John 4
and5 when you get it go ahead then
cometh he to a city of Samar area which
is called siker near to the parcel of
ground that Jacob gave to his son Joseph
so now he came to highlight a city of
Samaria highlight that skip down my
brother skip down to verse seven 7 to9
go ahead there cometh a woman of Samaria
to draw water Jesus sath unto her give
me to drink for his disciples were gone
away unto the city to buy me then sayth
the woman of Samaria unto him how is it
that thou being a Jew askest drink of
meat which am a woman of Samaria for the
Jews have no dealings with the
Samaritans and this is why we know that
the woman was not an Israelite Jesus was
a Jew of the an is Israelite of the
tribe of Judah you know
so and he told the woman recognized that
the Jews did not have no dealing with
the Samaritan because they were two
different nations let me show you what
I'm talking about let's go to 2 Kings
the 17th chapter Second Kings
17 how did she get there to Samaria
Second Kings
17 Second Kings 17 begin at verse
one in the 12th year of ahaz king of
Judah began HOSA the son of Eli to reign
in Samaria over Israel nine years all
right soos was a king over Israel skip
down to verse three and go ahead against
him came up shalaman King of Assyria and
HOSA became his servant and gave him
presents skip all the way down to 24 and
go
ahead and the king of Assyria brought
men from Babylon and from Black Nation
ham hamic Nation of the children of ham
go ahead and from Ava and from Black
Nation all
these Assyria black Babylon which is
shinar Black Nation okay then he brought
men from CA up the Euphrates black
nation and then other people from ABA go
ahead and from HTH uhuh and from from
safam and from them in the cities of
Samaria and and place them and place
them place them in the cities of Samaria
go ahead instead of the children of
Israel and they possessed Samaria and
deal and dwelt in the cities thereof and
that's why she thought that she was
whatever she thought she was but she was
not an
Israelite so her ancestors were placed
there by
Shaman uh when he wared against Israel
and B them other nations the Assyria
took Israel out of the land and Sham
bought other men from other nations into
the land and so no she was not an
Israelite I hope that
helped can I throw something in yes sir
sir well you know and the Lord sent
lions in there to kill those people then
the people sent back to the king of
Assyria that the God of this land is
killing us because we don't know what
his rules are that's right then the king
the king of Assyria sent a levite there
to teach them the word of God yeah but
it said that but he feared God but every
one of them still serve their own God so
that's why this woman could get this
teaching from like maybe she might be an
Israelite but Jesus gave you an absolute
uh uh uh commandment to let you know
that this woman could not be an
Israelite let's go to Matthew the 10th
chapter read verse one skip down and
read verses 5 and six yep Matthew
10 uh
one and when he had called unto him the
12 disciples he gave them power against
unclean spirits to cast them out and to
heal all manner of sickness and all
manner of
diseases now skip down to five and
six okay then Jes then I'm sorry these
12 Jesus sent forth and commanded them
saying go not into the way of the
Gentiles and into any city of the
Samaritans enter ye not but go rather to
the law sheep of the House of
Israel so now if she was an Israelite
then she would have been included but
the Lord said oh enter into no city of
Samaria neither go to the Gentile but go
rather to the L sheep of the House of
Israel okay there you go all right good
add on thank you for that hope that
answered their question as we move on to
our
next H yes next question Serena Kendall
asks are the two anointed ones also the
two Olive branches referred to in
Zechariah 4 verse 12 and 14
Jesus and the Holy
Spirit all right brother Jerome share
some
light um the the the the two Olive um
branches or the two anointed ones that
you read about in uh Zechariah 4 they're
not Jesus or the Holy Spirit okay
they're going to be two flesh and blood
men and those flesh and blood men their
prophecies which you read about in
Revelations they're going to be
killed okay and you know Jesus can't be
can't die and the Holy Spirit can't be
killed okay so but let's go read those
verses that you gave in that
Zechariah uh Zechariah 4 verse 12 and
14 you get it go ahead and read and I
answered again and said unto him what be
these two Olive branches which through
the two golden pipes empty the golden
oil out of
themselves then said he these are the
two anointed ones that stand by the lord
of the whole earth yeah now let's go
read about them in the revelations the
11th
chapter and pick it up at verse three
and four and
Skip when you get it go ahead and read
and I will give power unto my two
witnesses and they shall prophesy
1,23 score days clothed in sackcloth
uhhuh that's doing a Great Tribulation
skip down to verse seven read to the
eight and when they shall have finished
their testimony the Beast that ascendeth
out of the bottomless pit shall make war
against them and Shall Overcome them and
kill them that's why I know they can't
be Jesus or the Holy Spirit next verse
and their dead bodies shall lie in the
street of the great city which
spiritually is called Sodom and Egypt
where also our Lord was
crucified okay that's all I got on
it yeah because at verse 42 say these
are the two olive trees and two
candlesticks standing before the god
of the
Earth all right thank you for that
brother as we continue to move
on uh yes we are now into tonight's Q&A
for
Wednesday August the 28
2024 Zion says it is said if we s
willfully there is no more sacrifice for
our sin
does that mean it's just over for us
what if we want to ask for
forgiveness how can we if God hear not
our
sin brother Dre can you um shed some
light on that yes sir let's go to that
um Hebrews 10 and we're going to read
verse uh
26 the thing
is when you understand all that that
Christ has done for
you and you go about to sin willfully
afterwards he's not going to continue to
be a sacrifice for
you this is what this is talking about
but go ahead and read it
brother for if we I'm sorry go ahead go
ahead brother for if we sin willfully
after that we have received the
knowledge of the truth truth there
remaineth no more sacrifice for sins
other words Christ ain't going to
continue to die for your
sins it's it's the book tells you
remissions of sins that are
passed you know you're not supposed to
just live a lawless Life coming into
this truth go ahead brother but a
certain fearful looking for of judgment
and Fire y indignation which shall
Devour the
adversaries he that despised Moses
Moses's law died without Mercy under two
or three
Witnesses of how much sore punishment
suppose ye shall he be thought worthy
who ha trotten down trotten underfoot
the Son of God and hath counted the
blood of the Covenant wherewith he was
Sanctified an Unholy thing and have done
despite unto the spirit of
Grace hey those that do that are counted
worthy of everything that they get in
the way of
punishment but we serve a merciful
god let's go to uh Ezekiel
18 let's go to Ezekiel
18 and pick it up at verse 26 brother
e 26 go ahead when you get it when a
righteous man turth away from his
righteousness and cometh iniquity and d
and dieth in them for for his iniquity
that he had done shall he die uhuh go
ahead again when the Wicked Man turneth
away from his wickedness that he has
committed and doeth that which is lawful
and right he shall save his soul he
shall save his soul when a wicked man
turn from his wickedness and do that
which is lawful and right why verse 28
go ahead because he
considerthe away from all his
transgressions that he hath committed he
shall surely live he shall not die skip
down to verse 31 brother go
ahead cast away from you all your
transgressions whereby ye have
transgressed and make you a new heart
and a new spirit for why will ye die oh
House of Israel how will you die why
would you sin
we after you come into
this go ahead verse
32 for I have no pleasure in the death
of him that dieth sayeth the Lord God
wellfor turn yourselves and live ye now
I got one last place let's go to
Ecclesiastes 9 and4 and that's it
Ecclesiastes 9 and4 read that when you
get there
brother for to him that is joined to all
the living there is hope for a living
dog is better than a dead lion that's
right because the living know the living
know that they going to die but the dead
don't know nothing so while you living
there is hope but God is
Judge and I would not it's a fearful
thing to fall into the hands of the
Living God when you doing wrong so I
would take that into consideration and
not sin willfully if it
all that's all sir got to fight that
flesh and put on the spirit brother D
yes sir thank you for that hope that
answered their question sister Deborah
time check for our next yes the time is
8:33 Carolyn Jenkins asks what is the
difference between the lease in the
Kingdom in Matthew 5 verse 19 to the
Kingdom in Matthew 11
verse1 all right least in the Kingdom
brother Julius go right ahead let's go
there brother James and read that
scripture least in the
Kingdom okay Matthew talking about the
Kingdom of Heaven which is the Father's
Kingdom New Jerusalem go ahead Matthew 5
19 yes sir whosoever therefore shall
break one of these least Commandments
and shall teach men so he shall be
called the least in the Kingdom of
Heaven but whosoever shall do and teach
them the same Shall be Called great in
the Kingdom of Heaven so now in this
context here that's the father's
Kingdom and in the father's kingdom is
for Spirit beings but you're GNA be in
the Lake of
Fire which will be in the Kingdom of
Heaven or you will be on the right side
with the father ruling and reigning with
Christ uh uh and with the father in The
Father's Kingdom so either way it go you
going to be in the Kingdom you going to
be in the Lake of Fire in the good side
or the or in the kingom uh uh ruling
with him in the father's Kingdom now
let's go to um
Matthew what's the other scripture 11 11
verse 11 go ahead let's pay attention to
this real good Matthew 11 And1 go ahead
verily I say unto you among them that
are born of women there have not risen a
greater than John the Baptist
notwithstanding he that is least in the
Kingdom of Heaven is greater than he so
now the key to this right here is
understanding among them that are born
of women so if you are born of women you
are a flesh and blood being so now it
says that
notwithstanding he that is least in the
Kingdom of Heaven is greater than he why
because spirit is greater than
flesh but in Matthew 5 he's showing you
that you're least in the Kingdom you're
in the Lake of
Fire
and in that same fifth chapter he you're
in the Kingdom of Heaven but you are in
Immortal either way it go let me show
you what I'm talking about let's go to
First Corinthians the 15th chapter
this this breaks it down real good First
Corinthians brother James the 15th
chapter okay 1 Corinthians 15 and let's
pick this up at verse 35 1 Corinthians
15 and 35 go
ahead but some man will say how are the
dead raised up and with what body do
they come so now we're talking about the
dead and now we're talking about the
resurrection of the Dead skip down to
verse 44 and go
ahead it is sown a natural body it is
sown a natural body that's the Flesh and
Blood body go ahead it is raised a
spiritual body go ahead there is a
natural body and there is a spiritual
body so now skip down to verse
53 for this corruptible must put on
incorruption and this Mortal must put on
immortality so now least to the kingdom
is you're in the Lake of Fire okay but
you are in the kingdom of God and if
you're righteous you are an immortal
being but you are in the kingdom of God
so now the book said this corruptible
that's that Flesh and Blood body must
put on immortality either way it go
you're going to be you're going to live
forever it's just a matter of where you
end up but the whole gist of it is
spirit is greater than flesh
I hope that
helped all right hope that answered your
question next question de next question
Malik Shakur asked for
explanation to Second Thessalonians 1
verse 6 is that saying that it's okay to
pray for tribulations against people
that's constantly bothering or bother
you brother wrong you do about the
people that's bothering you
constantly well let's go read the verse
CU I don't think it actually is saying
that let's go read the
verse 2 Thessalonians chapter 1 verse
6 seeing it is a righteous thing with
God to recompense tribulation to them
that trouble you yeah so that verse is
not
saying it's okay
for us to pray for
tribulation upon those that trouble us
the verse actually said it is a
righteous thing with God to
recompense tribulation the a righteous
judge you know so that's what that verse
is saying uh let's go to uh Romans
chapter
12 and I want to read verse
17-9 and I'll turn it over to the p uh
Romans chapter 12 verse
17-19 when you get it go ahead
recompense to no man evil for evil
provide things honest in the sight of
all men if it be possible as much as
lith in you live peaceably with all
men dearly beloved avenge not yourselves
but rather give Place unto wrath for it
is written vengeance is mine I will
repay sayeth the Lord yeah so yeah yeah
give it to the Lord he vengance belong
to him he'll he'll
recompense um that's all I got on
anybody want to add something that
can't well that's one other thing one
other thing you can look at Lord said
don't
rejoice when he is punishing your enemy
oh right because if you do he
stop yeah but doesn't mean you can't
pray for no punishment on it you just
pray that the Lord change him but if the
Lord start to bring drum on You drama on
them then you start to Rejoice then the
Lord say don't do that because if you do
then he going to startop Bringing drama
on you because why should he punish you
them uhh uh uh when you have become the
same thing that they are yeah no you
don't pray for the demise of
nobody
right all
right hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next question as
time is ticking yes Nesha Drummond asks
how do you change the negative energy in
the workplace and with family and where
in the Bible can I find
guidance all right well we we can't say
whether you ever be able to get rid of
the negative energy in the workplace or
in the family sometime that's just how
it is you can always pray that is
definitely a good thing to do let's go
to Matthews 5 right quick Matthews
5 if you walking with God got your game
tight do what verse
um 14 says here
are ye are the light of the world a city
that is set on an Hill cannot be hid
skip down to verse
16 let your light so shine before men
that they may see your good works and
glorify your father which is in heaven
so you make sure that you letting your
light shine wherever you go before men
that they may see your good works and
glorify your father which is in heaven
turn over to Philippians 2 Philippians
2 because sometimes you can't do nothing
about that negative energy that's there
D it was there long before you got there
and could be there after you gone but
you continue to make sure that you doing
what Philippians 2 and verse 12 and 13
say read it when you get there brother
wherefore my beloved as ye have always
obeyed not as in my presence only but
now much more in my absence work out
your own salvation with fear and
tribbling so you work out your own
salvation with fear go ahead read 13 for
it is it is God which worketh in you
both to Will and to do of this of his
good pleasure so you just keep on
letting your light shine continue to
work out your own salvation and hey
others around can see that light
sometime and if they care not to see it
you just keep working for your own
salvation that's all I
got all right hope that answered your
question is we move on as time is
ticking sister de yes Felicia asks are
these the souls that was beheaded after
the
144,000 in Revelation who had on white
robes Revelation 5 verse 11 so there
James you read it the guest caller is
going to share some light from there
Revelation 5 and verse
11 and I beheld and I heard the voice of
many angels round about the throne and
the Beast and the elders and the number
of them was 10,000 times 10,000 and
thousands of
thousands that don't have nothing to do
with the question that's tell you know
it's
uh you know the one that's got white
robes that is the rightousness of the
Saints let's go into Revelation 7
chapter Revelation chapter 7 and read
verses four and Skip down and read verse
n and I heard the number of them which
were sealed and there were
sealed 140 and 4,000 of of all the
tribes of the children of
Israel verse 9 after this I beheld and
LW a great multitude which no man could
number of all the nations and kindreds
and people in tongues stood Before the
Throne and before the lamb clothed with
white robes and Psalms and and Palms in
their in their
hands now let's go to R Revelations 19th
Chapter and let's see what these white
robes represent Revelation 19 read verse
6-8 Revelation 19 Verse 6 and I heard as
it were the voice of a great multitude
and as the voice of many Waters and as
the voice of Mighty thunderings saying
Allelujah for the Lord God on nipotent
reth let us be glad and rejoice and give
honor to him for the marriage of the
Lamb is come and his wife ha made
herself ready and to her was granted
that she would that she should be
arrayed in fine linen clean and white
for the fine linen is the righteousness
of
saints so the whole thing is the 144,000
they didn't die they and the number that
couldn't That Couldn't number they did
not die those are the on that came
through the Great Tribulation they
wasn't even in the first
resurrection and uh they are there
though because when it said blessed
those that called to the marriage of the
Lamb because doing that that marriage
going to take a thousand
years and the ones that make it they
going to make it through their
righteousness and that's what's going to
be and their righteousness is
represented by fine linen white and
clean that's all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one yes Deborah
David asks why is no fire used on the
Sabbath day because that's what God
commanded that no fire be used on the
Sabbath day but let's go and read
that 35 and one Exodus 35
and when you get there read that verse
one and Moses gathered all the
congregation of the children of Israel
together and said unto them these are
the words which the Lord hath commanded
that ye should do them or commanded go
ahead six days sh work shall work be
done but on the seventh day there shall
be to you an holy day a Sabbath of rest
to the Lord whosoever doeth work therein
shall be put to death M ye shall Kindle
no fire throughout your habitations upon
the Sabbath day so that's why you don't
use no fire on the Sabbath day the Lord
commanded it and you must be
obedient all
right moving to our next question moving
on Stephen gugus asks are there any
precepts to Isaiah
28:9 and
10 it's going to read that Isaiah 28
let's open it up to the panel Isaiah 28
and when we get there we're going to
read that verse 9 and
10 I take it that's go and the best
caller will weigh in from
there okay Isaiah
289 Whom Shall he he teach knowledge and
Whom Shall he make to understand
Doctrine them that are weaned from the
milk and drawn from the breast for
precept must be upon precept precept
upon precept line upon line line upon
line here a little and there a
little so now the precept he's talking
about is the order that you use to teach
people knowledge yes first is talking
about weing from the milk and the breast
let's go and see what this what that
mean let's go into uh uh first Peter
2 and
two first Peter 2 and
two as newborn babes desire the sincere
milk of the word that ye may grow
thereby
so let you know you have to study the
words you can't deal with the uh uh with
somebody's opinion you can't deal with a
bunch of outline
books out books that are not coming out
of the Bible you must study the word
that's what you got to study so you can
grow by it that's the first move second
one you got to writefully divide the
scripture in other words you got to line
them up directly so the scripture
can uh uh uh explain what God is talking
about let's go into second Timothy
second chapter and read verse
15 second
Timothy what was
the second chapter and verse
15 study to show thyselves approved un
to God a Workman that needeth not to be
ashamed rightfully dividing the word of
Truth so that's what you got to do you
got to
study and you got to rightfully divide
the word of Truth in other words you
don't do no interpretation you let the
bible teach
you and the third
step is uh
Isaiah 8th chapter
verse 19 and
20 Isaiah
8 verse 19 and
[Music]
20 and when and when they shall say unto
you seek unto them that have familiar
spirits and unto Wizards that Peep and
that mutter should not a people seek
unto their God for the living to the
dead to the law and to the testimony if
they speak not according to this word it
is because there is no light in
them what the precept here is you got to
study the
Bible and you got to put the scripture
together and you got to use both
Testaments you can't be no Old Testament
scholar and no New Testament Christian
oh you got to go here a little and there
a little line up on line precept upon
precept they preach on the line and not
in between the line and you deal with
the word and not the Apocrypha and the
Book of Enoch and all them other
books so that is the precept study the
word find to worry about putting
scripture to scripture and use both Old
and New Testament that is the precept
that's put forth here all I have to say
yep hope that answered your question
there as we continue to move on
sister to the next one yes obey Jesus
says if we have knowledge of certain
things people or places being
idolist should we partake or associate
with them or in them even if it's not
just food and they give first corini 10
vers 27 and 28
let's go there brother James 1
Corinthians
1027 and
28 if any of them that believe not bid
you to a feast and ye be disposed to go
whatsoever is set before you eat asking
no questions for conscience sake but if
any man say unto you this is offered and
sacrificed unto Idols eat not for his
sake that showed it and for conscious
sake for the Earth is the Lords and the
fullness thereof yes
carer well the first thing is if you be
somebody some you know Paul is talking
from the standpoint of people that that
know about the dinary law that's
right ain't going to put nothing on
there that you shouldn't eat however
if they say that this Feast is some God
then you don't participate so same thing
if somebody uh invite you to something I
don't know what the function is if it's
not honoring uh uh if it's honoring some
God uh-uh if it's not just a regular
function why not that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question sister Deborah time is ticking
next yes Kyle says in Acts
7: 55 and 56 did Stephan actually see
Jesus standing on the right hand of the
father or was this a vision of the
future based on Psalms 110 verse1 or had
the father already made Jesus enemies
his foot stol after Jesus
resurrected what you say brother
Julius I didn't get that question I
apologize I didn't get that
question okay all right let's uh let's
keep it moving in Sister Deborah we'll
uh rework that one back in so please
stay tuned with us next week if we don't
get to it tonight what's our next
question sister all right uh Bobby Reed
asks is it okay to participate in a
dinner for my deceased sister on her
birthday yes carer can they participate
in a dinner for their deceased sister on
her
birthday it depends on what they doing
if they said that we going to Feast with
our sister and and we know that she's
here then no but if it just as a it's
just as a memorial of a birthday why not
that's yeah yeah and and I wouldn't go
if it was in the cemetery either
all right hope that answered your
question and let's move on to the next
one all right uh uh brother Anthony
horsey
says who who were the
samarians and I think you really
answered that uh very well it was either
Julius or Dre but who were the Samaran
Samaritans and why did the Jews not deal
with them there okay there was a group
of Sunday followers on Facebook saying
that they were Israelites of the
northern kingdom couldn't find it in the
book please share some light that light
was shared it on yeah that was brother
Julius you you gota you gotta come back
for that one we can only go with what
the book go ahead guest caller y guest
caller J already answered that right so
moving on uh TX Domino says need some
clarification on Luke 16 vers 16 and
17 and Ephesians 2 vers 15 and 16 I've
been going over and over the verses and
can't seem to get around
them all right so let's see how the
guest caller can share some light this
uh it's probably coming up to our last
question or next to it Luke 16 and verse
16 and 17 when you get there brother
James the law and the prophets were
until John since that time the kingdom
of God has preached and every man
presses into it and it is easier for
heaven and earth to pass than one little
of the law to
failm okay we deal with that uh uh real
quick John Luke 16 And1
17 let's let's uh uh uh go into Matthews
the 11th
chapter Matthews 11 okay read vers
12-4 Matthew 11:1
12-14 and from the days of John the
Baptist until now the Kingdom of Heaven
suffereth violence and the violent take
it by force for all the prophets and the
law prophesied unto John and if ye will
receive it this is Elias which was for
to
come now John the Baptist he came in the
spirit of Elijah but it already
prophesied that he was going to come
let's go in there let's go into uh uh
uh Malachi the 4th
chapter read verse five and
six Malachi the 4th chapter verses 5 and
six behold I will send you Elijah the
prophet before the coming of the great
and Dreadful day of the Lord for he
shall turn the heart of the fathers to
the children and the Heart of the
children to their fathers least I come
and smite the Earth with a
curse so have this have a two man and
John the Baptist came and he was Elijah
because he came in the spirit of
Elijah but then laen spoke also about
the great and terrible day but we just
dealing with the beginning
represented uh dealing with John the
Baptist and who is this John the Baptist
let's go to Malachi 3 1
and2 Malachi 31 and2 behold I will send
my messenger and he shall prepare the
way before me and the Lord whom you seek
shall suddenly come to his Temple even
the messenger of the Covenant whom you
Delight in behold he shall come sayith
the Lord of hosts but who may abide the
days of his coming and who shall
stand now he going to send his message
before his face and that and then the
Lord whom you seek shall come to
certainly come to his Temple now the
messenger in Jesus day was John the
Baptist John the Baptist is the last
recorded Prophet you have in the new
book you have somebody said this was a
prophet and that was a prophet but no
John the Baptist was the one that came
and prepare you for the coming of Jesus
in the beginning it in the first time
and then you can have a whole lot of
people out here in the spirit of Elijah
preparing the people to prepare for the
coming of the Lord even before the great
and turble day of the Lord that is when
he come the
second so now John the Baptist truly was
the last
prophet all right
and sister Deborah we're going to close
out what was that last scripture they
had Ephesians
what um EP oh yes it was Ephesians 2
vers 15 and 16 all right can you go
there brother James read that and the
guest caller will close out our program
with the light shined on those two
verses Ephesians 2 ver 15 and 16 correct
yes
sir having abolished in his flesh the
enity even the law of the Comm of even
the law of Commandments contained in
ordinances for to make in himself of
Twain one new man so making peace and
that he might reconcile both unto God
and one body by the cross having slain
the imity
thereby now this this is talking about
coming of Jesus and when he and when he
uh uh uh come let's go Ephesians right
quick and read verse 11 through 20 well
we ain't going to do all that just start
at verse 11 Ephesians 2
And1 wherefore remember that ye being in
the time past Gentiles In the Flesh who
are called un circumcision by that which
is called the circumcision in the flesh
made by hand
that at the time ye were without Christ
being aliens from the Commonwealth of
Israel and strangers from the covenants
of Promise having no hope and without
God in the world but but now in Christ
Jesus ye who were sometimes or who
sometimes were far off are made nigh by
the blood of Christ for he is
our that that that's the that mean that
you become a part of the household let's
go to one last place Galatians
3 and
26-29 this is really what it sums up to
26 and
29 or ye are all the children of God by
faith in Christ Jesus for as for as many
of you have been baptized into Christ
have put on Christ there is neither Jew
nor Greek there is neither Bond nor free
there is neither male nor female for ye
are all one in Christ Jesus and if ye be
Christ then are ye Abraham's seed and HS
according to the
promise that's all Paul's saying said
now you're Gentiles In the Flesh you've
been about allowed to become a part of
the Commonwealth of Israel through Jesus
if you Christ
then and El according to the promise
have nothing to do with keeping the law
or breaking the law it has something to
do with serving the lord of course if
you're gonna do You're Gonna Keep The
Commandments that's all I have to say
all right all right we hope that that
answered your question there as that has
brought us to the end of our program and
we'd like to say to everybody that if
you sent in some questions and we didn't
have a chance to get to them please do
not resubmit them because the questions
you have sub commed sister Deborah take
it put it in rotation and we will deal
with those questions next Wednesday so
we want to thank you all for tuning in
with us and until we come together again
we ask that you all be safe and be
blessed and brother James is going to
close us
out Our Father which art in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our debts as we forgive
our debtors and lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus name we pray
amen amen amen amen good night all night
good night